{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Vertical Blinds Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62493/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62493,"taskName":"Vertical Blinds - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Vertical Blinds","xmTaskDescriptor":"Vertical Blinds Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Blinds replace vertical window","textMessagingName":"Install Vert Blinds","rolloverLongDesc":"Mostly handled by specialty firms that install what they sell. Usually only a handyman service will install window treatments the consumer has purchased on their own.","rolloverShortDesc":"Mostly handled by specialty firms that install what they sell.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Vertical Blinds.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Vertical Blind Installation and Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Vertical Blinds Installation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Vertical Blinds - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Vertical Window Blinds Project","urlName":"Vertical-Blind-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Vertical Blinds Installers in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Blinds replace vertical window treatments","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9065,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62493/":{"taskOID":62493,"originalTaskOID":62493,"setID":9065,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500701,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503197,"questionDisplayText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden","answerDisplayText":"Wooden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"PVC (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"PVC (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1090,"questionDisplayText":"Special features requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you want to have installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500701,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503197,"questionDisplayText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of vertical blinds do you want installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden","answerDisplayText":"Wooden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"PVC (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"PVC (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden","answerDisplayText":"Wooden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"PVC (plastic)","answerDisplayText":"PVC (plastic)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1090,"questionDisplayText":"Special features requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you want to have installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}